What would you say was some of
the most pivotal things that you incorporated,
whether it was into your
routine or just throughout your life,
for self-improvement and personal development that
led you to where you are today?
You know, I think for
any entrepreneur, it's always a challenge,
and it definitely was for me, keeping life-work balance.
And now, even more so
as I'm older, it's life-health-work balance.
And I started very young, I had children very young,
and I had a high-tech, super-successful company very young.
Through that process, I ended up divorced early on.
Some of that was with the stress
of starting a company and having young children
and having a young marriage.
And that was where I think
some of that life-work balance broke down.